声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：憨妹  youko 七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
对不起  伙计  我知道这很不好受
Sorry, man. I know this hurts.
你是徒手把子弹取出来的
you pulled the bullet out with your bare hands.
有时间你一定要再给我演示一下
You have to show me how to do that sometime.
-什么  我不会...  -她在哪儿
-What? I didn't...  -Where is she?
你是说Kate
You mean Kate?
她连着24小时一直在照看你
She's been watching over you for the past 24 hours straight.
唯一能让她休息的办法
The only way I could get rid of her
就是让她出去给你弄点吃的
was to send her out to get some food for you.
我爱她
I love her.
小妞
Hey, girl.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
你好啊
Hey, there.
好了  我扶你到床上去
All right, let's get you to the bed.
当心脚下  当心点
Watch your step, watch your step!
什么味道这么难闻
What the hell is that smell?
-是你呼出来的  -是的
-Probably your breath.  -Yeah, right.
快点
Come on.
你真漂亮
You're beautiful.
我刚才称赞你了
I just gave you a compliment.
是的  我听见了
Yeah, I heard you.
你怎么不先把我裤子脱下来
Aren't you gonna take my pants off first?
你真漂亮
You are beautiful.
晚安
Good night.
咖啡  馅饼  还是两个都要
Coffee, pie? Both?
来杯啤酒怎么样
How about a beer?
让我看看身份证
I'd like to see some I.D.
我24岁了  妈妈
I'm 24, ma.
你又想不戴安全帽疯骑摩托
You want to ride around on that death trap of yours without a helmet.
我是不会让你喝醉的
I'm not going to help your cause by getting you drunk.
你手腕怎么了
How's that wrist?
什么  这个
What, this?
你也知道
You know,
厨房的那个架子有的时候会突出来
that shelf in the kitchen sticks out sometimes.
虽然我会记得它在那儿  但我还是撞了上去
You'd think I'd remember it was there, but I banged it...
别骗我了
Don't.
别管我的事  Katherine
I made my bed, Katherine.
你的房子已经不在了  妈妈
Well, your bed's gone, ma.
什么
What?
-这是什么  -这栋房子的保险
-What is this?  -An insurance policy for the house.
-什么  我从来没有...  -我以你的名义取出来的
-What? I never...  -I took it out in your name.
你做了什么
What did you do?
Wayne 知道这事吗
Does Wayne know about this?
记住你一直在这里
Just remember that you were here
而且没有看到过我  好么
and you didn't see me, okay?
Katherine  你到底做了什么
Katherine, what did you do?
我是为你好  妈妈
I took care of you, ma.
我得走了
I gotta go.
你这一阵子不会再见到我了
You're not gonna see me for awhile.
Katherine
你做了什么
What did you do?
Katherine
你还好吗
Are you okay?
很好
Yeah.
我想我只是...
I think I'm just...
只是有点累了
I think I'm tired.
-他怎么样了  -还在发烧
-How is he?  -Fever's still up there.
也不知道抗生素有没有起作用
Can't tell if the antibiotics are working.
让他吃点东西会有好处
It'll help to get some food in him.
你应该去海滩上...
You should get down to the beach for...
参加Shannon的葬礼
for Shannon.
我觉得
I was actually thinking that
我留下来照顾Sawyer会更好
I should stay and watch Sawyer.
我来就行了
I'll stay with him.
你应该去那儿
You should be there.
不要让他缺水
Keep him hydrated.
把水果捣碎
Maybe mash upsome of that fruit,
看看能不能给他吃一点
see if you can get him to eat it.
每个人都会去海滩
And everybody will beat the beach,
所以别忘了那个按钮
so don't forget the button.
我知道了
I got it.
我马上回来
Be back in a couple of hours.
你确定你能行吗
You sure you're okay?
对  我可以
Yeah, I'm great.
我要去参加葬礼
I'm going to go to the funeral.
我想我不会去
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
我想大部分人会知道那是一个意外
I think most of them realize it was an accident.
Shannon和我互不相识
Shannon and I were strangers.
我们永远都不会相遇如果...
We never would have met if...
我们甚至都不会和对方说话如果...
we wouldn't even have spoken if...
但是我们确实相遇了  也说话了
but we did meet, and we did speak.
至少...
At least...
我爱她
I loved her.
愿她安息
May she rest in peace.
你饿吗
You hungry?
我正准备给你吃点水果
I'm just gonna mash you up some fruit here.
当你醒来的时候
When you wake up,
看见我在像喂婴儿一样喂你
you're going to get a kick out of me
你肯定会踹我
feeding you like a baby.
我看见了一匹马
I saw a horse.
是的
Yeah.
你缺乏睡眠就会这样
That's what happens when you don't sleep.
Sawyer
-你醒了吗  -毫无价值的...
-You awake?  -Good for nothing...
你杀了我
You killed me.
你为什么要杀我
Why did you kill me?!
是警报声
It's the alarm.
Kate
Sawyer
16 2...
-发生了什么  -我不知道
-What happened?  -I don't know.
-但是你说过...  -我不知道 John
-But you said...  -I don't know, John!
那么  Kate在哪
Well, where's Kate?
Kate
你没去参加葬礼
Hey,you missed the funeral.
对  我在照顾Sawyer
Yeah, uh, I was with Sawyer.
对
Oh, right.
新来的那些人  他们有几个也参加了
A  few of them came,the new people.
那个杀了Shannon的女人没去
Not her, the one who killed Shannon.
不然会很尴尬
That would have been awkward.
他们好像过得很不开心
They seem to have had a rough time of it.
就像在演苍蝇王这部电影一样
Looks like they went bloody "lord of the flies" out there.
我说的你一句都没听进去
You haven't listened to a word I've said.
你觉得这有马吗
Do you think there are horses here?
什么
What?
我想我在丛林里看见了一匹马
I think I saw a horse in the jungle.
我还看见过北极熊
I've seen polar bears.
我看见过怪物
I've seen monsters.
那么  是听到了怪物  但是马呢
Well, heard monsters.But horses?
没见到过
No.
Kate
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
塔拉哈西  单程票  谢谢
Tallahassee, one way, please.
塔拉哈西
Tallahassee?
我在塔拉哈西呆过一阵子
I spent a week in Tallahassee one night.
那儿都是大卖场和瓦芙屋
It's  all strip malls and waffle houses.
像你这样漂亮的女孩
What's a pretty girl like you
去塔拉哈西做什么
gonna do down in Tallahassee?
我去找点东西
I'm sure I'll find something.
你在那有家人  对吧
Bet you got family down there, huh?
事实上  我只是去逛逛
Actually, I'm just visiting.
我认识你吗
Don't I know you?
不  我们不认识
No, I don't think so.
别跑  Kate
Don't run, Kate.
我抓住她了
I got her.
Kate Austen  你因谋杀而被捕
Kate Austen,you're under arrest for murder.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
不  你犯法了
Yeah, you did.
是你妈妈把你供出来的  Kate
Your mama gave you up, Kate.
Charlie  你见过Kate了吗
Charlie, have you seen Kate?
刚才还在丛林里看见她
Uh, a little while ago in the jungle.
她有点奇怪
She was acting kind of balmy,
问我岛上有没有马
asking me about horses on the island.
你知道她现在在哪吗
You know where she is now?
她顺着这条路往山洞走了
She's on the path heading back to the caves.
有事么
Everything okay?
不  Charlie  一切都好
Yeah, Charlie, everything's fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
终于自由了  对吧
Free at last, huh?
是的  伙计
Yeah, man.
看上去不错
Looks good.
Locke
这些防爆门怎么了
What's up with the blast doors?
防爆门
Blast doors?
是的
Yeah.
如果真爆炸了
Like in case of an explosion,
它们会直接掉下来
they'll come from the ceiling.
下边的那个家伙
That guy down here
-Desmond  -对了  Desmond
-Desmond?-Yeah, Desmond.
他没告诉你它们是干什么用的
He didn't tell you about these, what they're for?
没有  他没说
No, no, he didn't,
但是他留下了一段影片
but he did leave a movie.
影片
A movie?
没错
Yeah.
你想看吗
You want to see it?
我也想看
I would like to see it, too.
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind.
当然可以
Why not?
人越多越好
The more, the merrier.
Kate  你到底在这干吗
Kate, what the hell are you doing out here?
舱子里发生了什么  Kate  你为什么离开了
What happened in the hatch, Kate? Why'd you leave?
我回去的时候发现Sawyer就这么躺在地上
I come back. I find Sawyer just lying on the ground.
-你就这么走了  -他还好吗
-You just took off.  -Is he okay?
对  Kate  他没事
Yes, Kate, he's fine.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
真的是你
Are you?
对  我很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉我并不像你那样完美
I'm sorry that I am not as perfect as you!
我很抱歉我没有那么出色
I'm sorry that I'm not as good!
-你到底怎么了  -算了
-What's going on with you?  -Just forget it.
-不  别走  不要  -让我走
-No, don't walk away from me, no.  -Let me go!
Kate  Kate  Kate  Kate
不  我...
Don't! I...
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
Kate
这个地方...这个地方太奇怪了
This place...this place is crazy.
我受不了了  我都要疯了
I can't. It's driving me nuts.
我知道  没事了
I know. It's okay.It's all right.
没事了
It's all right.
好么
All right?
Kate
从警报响起那一刻起
From the moment the alarm sounds,
你有四分钟时间向那台电脑
you will have four minutes to enter the code
输入那串数字
into the microcomputer processor.
来启动程序
Induction into the program.
当警报响起
When the alarm sounds,
你或你的搭档必须输入数字
either you or your partner must input the code.
强烈推荐给你
It is highly recommended that
你和你的搭档最好轮班
you and your partner take alternating shifts.
这样  你们就可以时刻保持警觉
In this manner, you will both stay as fresh and alert
最重要的就是当警报响起时
It is most important that when the alarm sounds,
密码要准确并及时的输入电脑
the code be entered correctly and in a timely fashion.
不要尝试使用电脑做任何事...
Do not attempt to use the computer for anything...
当你的替班到了之后
Until your replacements arrive,
此项目的成败将掌握在你的手里
the future of the project is in your hands.
我代表Degroots
On behalf of the Degroots,
Alvar Hanso和达摩启动计划中的所有同僚
Alvar Hanso and all of us at the Dharma Initiative,
向你们表示敬意和感谢
thank you, namaste,
祝你们好运
and good luck.
好了
All right.
那么每两个小时按一次按钮
So you've been pushing that button every two hours
那你自从下到这里后
since you got down here.
没错
That's right.
你是怎么做到的
How's that even work?
我安排了两人轮班
I've set up 2-person shifts,
每人六个小时  每个人都会轮到
6 hours. Everyone's on the roster.
他们不想知道为什么这么做吗
Don't they want to know why?
我想这个电影已经说得很清楚了
I think the film is pretty self-explanatory.
真的么
Really?
我只听到一些
All I heard was
关于电磁石和突发事件什么的
something about electromagnets and an incident.
少掉的那些部分呢
What about all the missing pieces?
你是说那些连接的部分
you mean the splices?
只是一帧一帧的画面
Yeah, just a frame here and there,
我觉得没什么重要的
I think, nothing important.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
对于那部电影  你怎么看
About the film, what do you think?
我很抱歉错过了她的葬礼
I'm sorry I missed it,her funeral.
我... 我得照顾Sawyer  所以...
I... I had to be with Sawyer, so...
你现在怎么没跟他在一起
Why aren't you with him now?
因为我快要疯了
'Cause I'm going crazy.
你相不相信鬼  Sayid
Do you believe in ghosts, Sayid?
就在Shannon被枪击之前我在丛林里看见了Walt
I saw Walt in the jungle just before Shannon was shot.
那有让我发疯么
Does that make me crazy?
去审讯室要开很长时间
It's a long drive back to the arraignment.
你还好吧
You comfy?
为什么是现在
Why now?
什么
What?
像你这样的农场乖女孩
Nice corn-fed farm girl like yourself,
没有暴力史  优等生
no history of violence,straight A's,
没有前科  只有几张超速罚单
no record,a couple of speeding tickets.
我只是好奇  为什么你现在要杀了他
I just gotta wonder,why'd you kill him now?
好了  还是别和我说了
Oh, right, yeah, don't tell me.
你不会想控告你自己的
You wouldn't want to incriminate yourself,
不然你不会精心策划了这一切
not after you were so smart planning it.
爱荷华州的陪审团肯定不会
That jury back in Iowa sure ain't gonna
在是否是预谋杀人上迟疑的
get hung upon premeditation.
放煤气是么
And a gas leak?
拜托  手法太幼稚了
Come on, it's amateur hour from top to bottom.
看上去你好像都已经明白了
It sounds like you've got it all figured out.
我倒是把你看透了
I do have you all figured out.
对于我你什么都不知道
You don't know anything about me.
你妈是离了婚的贫穷白种女人
White-trash mom divorces dad,
和一个酒鬼拍拖
starts up  with some guy who's a drinker,
也许他对她很粗暴
maybe he knocks her around a little bit,
之所以她嫁给他是因为  你知道的
and so she marries him because, you know,
发生了一些事
that's what happens.
然后这个酒鬼  Wayne
And then this drunk, this Wayne,
他搬进了你家
he moves into your house,
你就得每晚整理房间
and you get to lay there every night
听着他在那里干你妈
and listen to him doing your mom right there
在你爸的老卧室里
in your daddy's old bedroom.
这也许还不算很坏
And even that wouldn't be so bad
如果他没有一直打你妈妈
if he didn't beat her up all the time.
但是她爱他
But she loves him,
她为他辩护
she defends him.
如果这样还不能让一个人想要杀人
If that don't make a person want to kill somebody,
我就不知道什么能了
I don't know what does.
但问题是  现在
But the question is, now?
为什么是现在
Why now?
为什么这么多年以后
Why after all these years
你才决定要把可怜的Wayne干掉
did you just decide to blow poor Wayne up?
他晚上去敲你的门了
He come knocking on your door late at night?
他从来没碰过我
He never touched me.
小心
Look out!
滚...
Get...
滚下去
Get off!
你现在为什么不输数字呢
Why can't you just put the numbers in now?
不  现在输没用
No, it doesn't work that way.
警报在还剩四分钟时响起
The alarm goes off in four minutes.
到那时你才能输入
You can't type anything till then.
不介意我看看这些硬件吧
You mind if I check out some of this hardware?
当然
Sure.
别弄坏就好了
Just don't break it.
你好
Hello again.
Hello.
我想我有样东西你该看看
I have something I think you should see.
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind,
我将从头说起
I will begin at the beginning.
在耶稣之前很久的时候
Long before Christ,
犹太国国王是一个叫Josian的人
the king of Judah was a man named Josiah.
伙计  你说从头说起这头还真是久远
Boy, when you say "beginning,"you mean beginning.
那时候
At that time,
人们供奉神灵的神庙被毁了
the temple where the people worshipped was in ruin,
所以他们就崇拜偶像
and  so the people worshipped idols,
假的神灵
false gods,
所以国家一片混乱
and so the kingdom was in disarray.
因为Josian是个好国王
Josiah, since he was a good king,
他派他的大臣去藏宝藏的地方
sent his secretary to the treasury
说道
and said,
"我们必须重建神庙
"we must rebuild the temple.
"把所有的金子发给工人
Give all of the gold to the
"这样就能行了"
workers so that this will be done."
但是当大臣回来时
But when the secretary returned,
他并没有带着金子
he had no gold.
当Josian问为什么的时候
And when Josiah asked why this was,
大臣回答说...
the secretary replied...
"我们找到一本书"
"we found a book."
你听过这个故事吗
Do you know this story?
没有  恐怕没有
No, afraid I don't.
大臣找到的
What the secretary had found
是一本很老的书
was an ancient book,
律法书
the book of law.
你也许在圣经的旧约中听说过
You may know it as the Old Testament.
因为那本律法书
And it was with that ancient book,
而不是靠金子
not with the gold,
Josian还是建起了神殿
that Josiah rebuilt the temple.
在岛的另一边
On the other side of the island,
我们找到了一个和这里类似的地方
we found a place much like this.
在那个地方
And in this place,
我们找到了一本书
we found a book.
我相信那里面的东西
I believe what's inside there
对你有很大的价值
will be of great value to you.
Rose的丈夫是白人啊
So Rose's husband's white.
没看见过他过来吗
Didn't see that one coming.
你需要什么东西吗  Hurley
Is there something you need, Hurley?
只是随便走走
Just taking a walk,
来打个招呼
thought I'd say "hey."
谁在照看Sawyer
Who's taking care of Sawyer?
Sun
Sun is.
那么你  有点生他的气
So you're, like, mad at him?
我为什么会生Sawyer的气
Why would I be mad at Sawyer?
也许因为他老是生病
Maybe 'cause he's the one always comes down here
接着是Chops Wood  现在连你也快了
and chops wood and now you are.
就像瘟疫一样
It's, like, transference.
你现在是心理医生吗
What are you? A shrink now?
在精神病院别人就是这么叫我的
Well, that's what they call it in the mental hospital.
我没有生任何人的气
I'm not mad at anyone.
Jack在哪儿
Where's Jack?
我不知道
I don't know.
他没回来过
He didn't come back.
他有说过什么吗
Has he said anything?
Sawyer?
没有  他一直睡着
No, he's still sleeping.
你能照看他吗
Can you watch him?
-如果你有事那我可以...  -不不  我来吧
-I can stay if you...  -No. Yeah, I can.
谢谢
Thanks.
是的  我确定就是那张表
Yes, I'm sure that's the exact form you've got.
我会发一张给你  好吧
I'll send one over to you, right.
稍后打给你
I'll call you back later.
爸爸
Dad.
亲爱的  现在警察们
Kate, the police and the U.S.Marshals
都在通缉你
are looking for you.
你不应该来这里
You shouldn't have come here.
我已经在外面等了2个小时了
I've been waiting outside for 2 hours.
他们不在这里
They're not here.
他们说的是真的吗
Is it true what they're saying?
亲爱的  你来这儿干什么
Kate, what did you come here for?
你为什么不告诉我  爸爸
Why didn't you tell me, dad?
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
我在做照片剪辑
I was making a scrapbook,
准备你生日的时候给你个惊喜
a surprise for your birthday,
我给你的一个同事打了电话
so I called one of your C.O.s
得到了一些你穿制服的照片
to get some pictures of you in uniform.
他给我的那些照片背面有日期
The pictures that he sent me had dates on the back,
你在朝鲜的照片
photos of you in Korea
在我出生前的4个月
up until four months before I was born.
你为什么不告诉我Wayne才是我的亲生父亲
Why didn't you tell me that Wayne was my father?
为什么
Why?
我没有告诉你是因为我知道你会杀了他
I didn't tell you because I knew you'd kill him.
你的妈妈...
And your mother...
很爱他
loved him.
你5岁的时候
You were 5 years old.
我想带你和我一起过
I wanted to take you along with me.
她不让我这么做
She wouldn't let me.
那你为什么不杀了他
So why didn't you kill him?
因为我从没想过要杀人
Because I don't have murder in my heart.
我不得不打电话告诉他们你来过
I'm gonna have to call them.
一小时之后再打行么
Can I have an hour?
再见  爸爸
Bye, daddy.
你能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
Sawyer?
Wayne?
我大概是疯了
I'm probably crazy,
这不要紧
and this doesn't matter,
但是可能你当时在那儿
but maybe you're in there.
不知怎么你问过我一个问题
Somehow you asked me a question.
你问我为什么...
You asked me why I...
为什么我那么做
why I did it.
那并不是因为你赶走了我爸爸
It wasn't 'cause you drove my father away
或是你那样看待我
or the way you looked at me
亦或者是你打我妈妈
or because you beat her.
而是因为我恨你是我的一部分
It was 'cause I hated that you were a part of me,
由此我不能完美
that I would never be good,
由此我永远不能拥有美好的东西
that I would never have anything good.
并且每次我看着Sawyer
And every time that I look at Sawyer,
每次我都有些感觉
every time I feel something for him,
我看到了你  Wayne
I see you, Wayne,
让我觉得很恶心
and it makes me sick.
那是我听过的最甜蜜的话
That's about the sweetest thing I've ever heard.
Sawyer?
那该死的Wayne是谁
Who the hell is Wayne?
我在哪儿
Where am I?
在床上
A bunk bed?
是的  你是睡在床上
Yeah, you're in a bunk bed.
我们得救了吗
Are we saved?
没有  Sawyer
No, Sawyer.
还没有
Not yet.
怎么这么巧
What are the odds?
巧
The odds?
是啊
Yeah.
来  把这个按在桌上  按平
Here, hold this down on the table here, nice and flat.
我是说  想想看吧
I mean, think about it.
有人拍了这部影片
Somebody made this film.
有人又把它切了
Someone else cut this piece out.
我们坠机了
We crash.
飞机的两半
Two halves of the same plane
落在了岛上的不同位置
fall on different parts of the island.
你在那里  我在这里
You're over there. I'm over here.
现在那些失落的影片
And now here's the missing piece,
又回到了原来应该在的地方
right back where it belongs.
怎么这么巧啊
What are the odds?
不要把巧合错当成命运
Don't mistake coincidence for fate.
你一定是在说笑
You've gotta be kidding me.
往这儿走
Air lock's over this way.
好了  承认了吧
Come on, admit it.
我们已经获救了
We've been rescued.
你碰到了  抱歉
You got it? Sorry.
小心点
Watch yourself.
真他妈的
Son of a bitch.
小心点  好吗
Watch yourself, okay?
好的
Okay.
又回到老地方了
Home sweet home.
是的
Yeah.
我真的认为你是故意和我说笑呢
I really thought you were yanking my chain.
你一直在笑什么
What do you keep smiling at?
你该剪头发了
You need a haircut.
真的吗
Really?
也许你该带我回舱子里去
Maybe you ought to take me back inside.
你也看见了
You see that?
如果你说的是
If you mean the big-ass horse
站在丛林中的马  那我看到了
standing in the middle of the jungle then, yeah.
你认识那匹马吗  雀斑女
You know that horse, freckles?
是的  我认识
Yeah, I do.
龙舌兰酒加奎宁水
Tequila and tonic.
是你要喝的吧
That's your drink, right?
那滋补品呢?
Where's the tonic?
那东西我们存货不多
We're running a little low on mixers.
你确定舍得把它浪费在我身上
Sure you want to waste that on me?
我想你也应该喝一杯
I figured you could use a drink.
当然
I know I could.
你要试着说服我
You're gonna try to convince me that
这里没人恨我
everyone here doesn't hate me?
那你就先说服我
Only if you're gonna try to convince me
这个世界上没有女人是疯的
that every woman in the world's not crazy.
当警报响起
When the alarm sounds,
你或你的搭档必须输入数字
either you or your partner must input the code.
而且你和你的搭档最好轮班
It is highly recommended that you and your partner take alternating shifts.
这样你们就可以时刻保持警觉
In this manner, you will both still stay as fresh and alert.
最重要的就是当警报响起时
It is most important that when the alarm sounds,
密码要准确并及时的输入电脑
the code be entered correctly and in a timely fashion.
就是这儿了
Here it comes.
除了输入数字
Do not attempt to use the computer
不要尝试使用电脑做任何其他事情
for anything else other than the entering of the code.
它只有这么一个用途
This is its only function.
由于做3号站的工作而产生的隔绝感
The isolation that attends the duties associated with station 3,
会使你们试着利用电脑
may tempt you to try and utilize the computer
与外部世界联系
for communication with the outside world.
这是绝对不允许的
This is strictly forbidden.
一旦你们这么做了
Attempting to use the computer in this manner
就会危及整个计划的完整性
will compromise the integrity of the project and
更糟的是  可能引发另一起事件
worse, could lead to another incident.
我再说一遍
I repeat,
不要尝试使用电脑做任何其他事情
do not use the computer for anything
除了输入数字
other than entering the code.
那就恭喜你了
Congratulations.
当你的替班到了之后
Until your replacements arrive,
此项目的成败将掌握在你的手里
the future of the project is in your hands.
好啊
Hello?
你是谁
Who is this?
我是Micheal
This Michael.
你是谁
Who is this?
爸爸
Dad?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====